Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public programs records, circa 1995-2011 COR0003.5.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Program files, financial records, and calendar productions, 1994-2011; Series 1
  - Minnie Churchill, 2004 October 6; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Rachel Cohen/Reception with the DCJCC, 2004 October 10; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 2004 October 11; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Albert Hadley (Eye on Design), 2004 October 12; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - MES - Takacs String Quartet, 2004 October 15; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Steve Ross, 2004 October 18; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Philippa Glanville, 2003 October 19; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Adam Gornik with John Andrews, 2004 October 20; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, 2004 October - 2004 November; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Kentuck Knob, Fallingwater and Pittsburgh, 2004 October; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Richard Rhodes - Audobon, 2004 October 25; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Icelandic Musician/Reception, 2004 October 14; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Paul Goldberger, 2004 October 26; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Dinner at the Residence of the New Zealand Ambassador, 2004 October 27; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Night Day, 2004 September; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Cuban Interests Section Cancelled, 2004 November 30; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Kenneth Jay Lane, 2004 November 1; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Baby Jane Dexter/Cabaret Cancelled, 2005 November 10; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Brooklyn Museum oof Art/Bus Trip, 2004 November 4; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - MES - Ying Quartet, 2004 November 5; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Meryle Secrest on Joseph Duveen, 2004 November 8; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Peter Marks with John Andrews, 2004 November 9; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - William Christenberry, 2004 Novemeber 11; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 2004 November 15; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Robert Lee Morris, 2004 November 17; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Theodore Robinson Trip, 2004 November 19; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Alex Katz, 2004 November 22; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Douglas Wilson, 2004 November 23; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Day Night, 2004 November; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Visionary Art Museum/Bus Trip Cancelled, 2004 December 3; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Fashion Group/Rreception, 2004 December 2; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Robert Lehrman, 2004 Deecember 1; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Bill Stubbs I Hate Red, You're Fired, 2004 December 6; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Israel Jazz/Reception, 2004 December 9; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Eric Denker - Collecting Prints, 2004 December 13; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Festive Evening at the Embassy of Romania, 2004 December 14; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Couture Accessory Trip to NYC, 2004 December 10; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Historic Holiday Tour, 2004 December 15; Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Kentuck Knob Fallingwater, 2006 July 7; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - John Eaton, 2006 July 12; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Eric Denker, 2006 July 13; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Shore Garden Tour, 2006 July 14; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Evening at Venezuela, 2006 July 17; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Hillwood, 2006 July 18; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Mark Urman Half Nelson Cancelled, 2006 July 20; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Stanley Karnow, 2006 July 25; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Andrea Bruce and Dai Baker/WHNPA, 2007 July 27; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Mt. Vernon Cancelled, 2006 July 31; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Best Cellars University at the Corcoran, 2006 September; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - James Abbott Jansen, 2006 September 7; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Book Club: Melville - Moby Dick, 2006 September 14; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Contemporary Music Forum/Reception, 2006 September 17; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Sequoia Cruse, 2006 September 18; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Francois-Frederic Guy, 2006 September 25; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Carol Highsmith, 2006 September 26; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Clodagh with FGI, 2006 September 28; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Trip to NYC: Met at Whitney, 2006 September 29; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Tim Gunn, 2006 October 5; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Diinner at the Residence of Malta, 2006 October 6; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Ron Rosenbaum The Shakespeare Wars, 2006 October 10; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Book Club: Wharton - The House of Mirth, 2006 October 12; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - MES: Takacs Quartet, 2006 October 13; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Annie Leibovitz, 2007 October 15; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Robert Mangold, 2006 October 19; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Charlottesville Buss Trip, 2006 October 17; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Johansen International, 2006 October 22; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Richard Kurin - Hope Diamond Cancelled, 2006 October 23; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Claire Lise Cabaret Cancelled, 2006 October 26; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - The Barnes and Courbet at the Walters, 2006 October 27; Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - CANCELED April 20, 2004 FY2004 Philadelphia Antiques Show/ Bus Trip, 2004 April 20; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - L850 April 1, 2004 FY2004 Mimi Shapiro, 2004 April 1; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - April 8, 2004 FY2004 Dominique Browning, 2004 April 8; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - April 13, 2004 FY2004 Luxury Brands- FGI Reception and Panel, 2004 April 13; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - April 15, 2004 FY2004 Embassy Residences, 2004 April 15; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - April 14, 2004 FY2004 Distinguished Homes Tour, 2004 April 14; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - April 19, 2004 FY2004 Contemporary Music Forum, 2004 April 19; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Feb.9; Mar. 1,31 and Apr.26, 2004 FY2004 Art and Law Seminar with CCAD, 2004 February 9, March 1, April 26; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - April 27, 2004 FY2004 Architect's Homes Tour, 2004 April 27; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - May 4, 2004 FY2004 Romanian Violin Concert/Reception, 2004 May 4; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - May 1+2, 2004 FY2004 GMCW Rental, 2004 May 1-2; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - May 9, 2004 FY2004 US Marine Band Rental, 2004 May 9; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - May 10, 2004 FY2004 Cuban Elegance, 2004 May 10; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - May 3, 2004 FY2004 Nick Nicholson - Dudley Lecture, 2004 May 3; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - May 12, 2004 FY2004 May Knott Quartet, 2004 May 12; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - May 13, 2004 FY2004 Raymond Dobard - Quilts as Codes, 2004 May 13; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - May 17, 2004 FY2004 Richard Brown - Triumphs and Turkeys, 2004 May 17; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - May 18, 2004 FY2004 Jeannine O'Grady - Decoding Da Vinci Code, 2004 May 18; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - May 19, 2004 FY2004 Deb Waterman Johns, 2004 May 19; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - May 26, 2004 FY2004 Architectual Gems Tour, 2004 May 26; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - May 26, 2004 FY2004 Boud for Glory / Booksigning, 2004 May 26; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - May 27, 2004 FY2004 VMFA, Lewis Collection, Jefferson/ Bus Tour, 2004 May 27; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - June 1, 2004 Ken Ludwig, 2004 June 1; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - June 3, 2004 FY2004 Marc Copland - Hall Memorial Concert, 2004 June 3; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - June 7, 2004 FY2004 Madeline Deschamps / Empire Style, 2004 June 7; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - June 9, 2004 FY2004 Jenny Lind Concert / Reception, 2004 June 9; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - June 14, 2004 FY2004 Open Theatre, 2004 June 14; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - June 15, 2004 FY2004 Marlene Verplanck, 2004 June 15; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - June 17, 2004 FY2004 Philip Thomson at the Russian Residence, 2004 June 17; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - June 22, 2004 FY2004 WHNPA: Michael Robinson-Chavez, 2004 June 22; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - June 23, 2004 FY2004 Kati Marton, 2004 June 23; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - June 25, 2004 FY2004 Joel Siegal Memorial Rental, 2004 June 25; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - June 24, 2004 FY2004 Sally Mann, 2004 June 24; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - June 25, 2004 FY2004 Art Deco Dangerous Liasons / Bus Tour, 2004 June 25; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - June 28, 2004 FY2004 Edith Piaf, 2004 June 28; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - January 2005 Newspaper Clippings, 2005 January; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - January 13, 2005 FY2005 Caio Fonseca, 2005 January 13; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - January 18, 2005 FY2005 Lindsay Moran Under Cover, 2005 January 18; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - January 24, 2005 Diane Von Furstenberg, 2005 January 24; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - January 26, 2005 FY2005 Mary Lynn Kotz Rauschenberg, 2005 January 26; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - January 27, 2005 FY2005 Mes-Gryphon Trio, 2005 January 27; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - January 25, 2005 FY22005 Chermayeff Geismar, 2005 January 25; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - CANCELED February 1, 2005 FY2005 Citizen Girl, 2005 February 1; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - February 3, 2005 FY2005 Math and the Mona Lisa, 2005 February 3; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - February 9, 2005 FY2005 Chinese Opera, 2005 February 9; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - February 10, 2005 FY2005 Michael Cullen on Christo and Jeanne Claude, 2005 February 10; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - February 11, 2005 FY2005 Mes-Jupiter Quartet, 2005 February 11; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - February 14, 2005 FY2005 F. Murray Abraham, 2005 February 14; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - February 16, 2005 FY2005 Arachne Aerial Arts, 2005 February 16; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - February 18, 2005 FY2005 Moma and the Gates / Bus Trip to NYC, 2005 February 18; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Mona / Gates Packet - 2/18/05, 2005 February 18; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - February 21, 2005 FY2005 Moma and the Gates #2/ Bus Trip to NYC, 20055 February 21; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - February 22, 2005 FY2005 Adademy Awards Program, 2005 February 22; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - February 23, 2005 FY2005 David Moser, 2005 February 23; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - March 2, 2005 FY2005 Adamstein Demetriou Architecture Tour, 2005 March 2; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - March 9, 2005 FY2005 Contemporary Music Forum, 2005 March 9; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - March 11, 2005 FY2005 Dali Trip, 2005 March 11; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - March 15, 2005 FY2005 Environmental Film Festival Oscar Niemeyer, 2005 March 15; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Egyptian Days and Nights/Reception, 2005 June 13; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Dinner at the Residence, 2005 June 3; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Donal Leace Cancelled!, 2005 June 15; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Embassy of France, 2005 June 17; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Annadel Rich Rental, 2005 June 21; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Urban Architecture Tour, 2005 June 21; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Wouter Van Baalen, 2005 June 23; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Chanel Trip To NYC, 2005 June 24; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Loose Documents, Circa 2005; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Scott Tilden - Architeecture for Art Cancelled, 2005 July 7; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Mass Ave Church Tour, 2005 July 6; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Newmyer - Jane Austen, 2005 July 11; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Scott Simon with Joe Barber, 2005 July 12; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Forlana Consort and Reception by the Belgium Embassy, 2005 July 14; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Maureen Orth, 2005 July 19; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Katzen Art Center Tour, 2005 July 21; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Sequoia, 2005 July 25; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - John Eaton, 2005 July 26; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Cezanne/Pissaro at MoMA Cancelled, 2005 August 5; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - American Impressionism in Connecticut Overnight Trip, 2005 August; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Woolly Mammoth Tour, 2005 September 22; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Michael Kimmelman, 2005 September 8; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Hillman Curtis, 2005 September 12; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel, 2005 September 14; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Design Trip to NYC, 2005 September 16; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 2005 September 18; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Air Force Rental, 2005 September 17; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Evening at the Residence of the Austrian Ambassador, 2005 September 21; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Lynn Redgrave - Nightingale, 2005 September 28; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Ambassadorial Event/Reception, 2005 September 29; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Mike Seeger, 2006 January 30; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Best Cellars University, 2006 January - 2006 February; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Michael Lasser "Ringing the Banjo" Cancelled, 2006 January 26; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Book Club: Adam Goodheart on Johnn Berendt's The City of Falling Angels, 2006 January 23; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Klaviertrio Amsterdam, 2006 January 20; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Michael Smith Elements of Style, 2006 January 18; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Robert Macneil Do you Speak American, 2006 January 17; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Book Club: Walter Kirn on E.L. Doctorow's The March Cancelled, 2006 February 27; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Baltimore Architecture Tour Rescheduled from December 9, 2006 February 24; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - A Taste of Mexican Art, 2006 February 23; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - A Parisian Valentine Cabaret, 2006 February 15; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Nevermore with Signature Theatre, 2006 February; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Brentano Quartet, 2006 February 10; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Philip Conisbee on Cezanne, 2006 February 8; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 2006 February 5; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Tour of the New Residence of the Ambassador of Switzerland, 2006 February 4; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Modern Art in New York/Bus Tour Cancelled, 2006 February 2; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Takacs Quartet, 2006 March 31; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Ziva Spanish Dance, 2006 March 29; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Book Club: Edward Hower on Hosseini's The Kite Runner, 2006 March 27; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Deborah Davis, 2006 March 23; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Robert Bechtle, 2006 March 22; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Evnvironmental Film Festsival Ernest Hemmingway: Rivers to the Sea, 2006 March 20; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - William J. Broad The Oracle, 2006 March 13; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Fashion in Color Bus Trip to NYC, 2006 March 10; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Parker String Quartet, 2006 March 3; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Dinner at the Residence of the Ambassador of Portugal, 2006 March 1; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Deborah Boily, 2005 March 16; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - MES - Prazak Quartet, 2005 March 17; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Lynn Redgrave, 2005 March 21; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Best Cellars University, 2005 March; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Vocally Swedish, 2005 March 23; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Ziva Spanish Dance, 2005 March 30; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - The Barnes and Winterthur/Bus Tour, 2005 April 1; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Andre Baeyens Clark and Paris, 2005 April 7; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Twilight Concert in the Salon Dore, 2005 April 10; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Curatorial Conversations, 2005 April - 2005 May; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Dinner at the Residence of the Ambassador of Norway, 2005 April 14; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 2005 April 18; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Mark Athitakis Cancelled, 2006 April 27; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Charleston, 2005 April; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Robert Mankoff, 2005 April 28; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Meet the Dutch Tour At the Dutch Ambassador's Residence, 2005 April 28; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Gay Men's Chorus of Washington - Rental, 2005 April - 2005 May; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Private Collections/Bus Tour, 2005 April 27; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Black Tie Benefit Dinner at the French Ambassador's Residence, 2005 May 3; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Dudley Lecture - James Cuno, 2005 May 5; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Marine Band Rental Cancelled, 2005 May 15; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Evening at the Swedish Ambassador's Residence, 2005 May 10; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Liz Smith Dishing, 2005 May 11; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Olga Hirshhorn Collection Tour, 2005 May 17; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - World Bank Happy Hour, 2005 May 19; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Francine du Plessix Gray, 2005 May 18; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Loose Newsletter, Circa 2005; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Mina Marefat, 2005 May 24; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Art and Style of Entertaining with FGI, 2005 May 26; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Caroline Milbank - Chanel, 2005 June 1; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Adamstein Demetriou Tour, 2005 June 2; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - WHNPA Talk/Eyes of HIstory, 2005 Viewing, 2005 June 7; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Rene Hofstede, 2005 June 8; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Jenny Lind/Reception, 2005 June 9; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Edward Dolnick The Rescue Artist, 2005 October 17; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Steve Ross, 2005 Octobr 19; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Best Cellars in the North Atrium, 2005 October 20; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Jupiter Quartet, 2005 October 21; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Dominique Browning The New Garden Paradise, 2005 October 25; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Jenny Holzer, 2005 October 26; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Monet's London/Bus Trip, 2005 October 28; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Yeohlee Lecture and Fashion Show, 2005 October 6; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - James River Plantation, 2005 October 14; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Concert of Ancient Greek Music, 2005 October 16; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Vincent Fremont Cancelled, 2005 November 9; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Oscar de la Renta/Andre Leon Talley, 2005 November 1; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Henrietta Spencer Churchill, 2005 November 2; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Sam Gilliam and Lowery Sims, 2005 November 2; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 2005 November 6; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Albert Hadley and Adam Lewis, 2005 November 8; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Gilliam at the Mateyka Gallery, 2005 November 16; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Dinner at the Residence of the Ambassador of Greece, 2005 November 17; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Garth Newel Piano Quartet, 2005 November 18; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Walter Isaacson, 2005 November 21; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Spring/Summer Fashion Preview, 2005 December 1; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Bunny Williams Cancelled, 2005 December 8; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Holiday Trip to NYC, 2005 December 2; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Kitty Carlisle Hart with John Andrews, 2005 December 5; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Evening at the Residence of the Ambassador of Brasil, 2005 December 6; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Designing for Democracy: A 3rd Century Mall, 2005 December 7; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Joanne Schmoll - Cabaret Concert, 2005 December 12; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Historic Hotel Holiday Tour Cancelled, 2005 December 14; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - December Public Program Calendar, 2005 December; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - November Public Program Calendar, 2005 November; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - October Public Program Calendar, 2005 October; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - September Public Program Calendar, 2005 September; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - July Public Program Calendar, 2005 July; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - June Public Program Calendar, 2005 June; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - May Public Program Calendar, 2005 May; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - April Public Program Calendar, 2005 April; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - March Public Program Calendar, 2005 March; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - February Public Program Calendar, 2005 February; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - January Public Program Calendar, 2005 January; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - CANCELED October 11, 2007 FY2008 Joseph Cornell's Dreams FY2008, 2007 October 11; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - October 12, 2007 FY2008 Mes: Ariel Quartet, 2007 October 12; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - October 15, 2007 FY2008 Eva Maddox: The Value of Design in Society, 2007 October 15; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - October 18, 2007 FY2008 Perspective Talk: Paul Roth, 2007 October 18; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - October 20, 2007 FY2008 Agents of Change: Ansel Adams Panel Discussion, 2007 October 20; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - CANCELED October 26, 2007 FY2008 Magnificent Landscapes Bus Tour, 2007 October 26; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - October 24, 2007 FY2008 Maxwell Mackenzie, 2007 October 24; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - October 28, 2007 FY2008 Contemporary Music Forum, 2007 October 28; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - November 2, 2007 FY2008 Nes: American Chamber Players, 2007 November 2; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - November 8, 2007 FY2008 Black White + Gray, 2007 November 8; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - November 13, 2007 FY2008 Edward Burtynsky, 2007 November 13; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - November 15, 2007 FY2008 Perspective Talk: George Pitts, 2007 November 15; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - November 26, 2007 FY2008 Cinematic Portraits By Jeremy Blake, 2007 November 26; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - November 27, 2007 FY2008 Steve Ross Cabaret, 2007 November 27; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - November 28, 2007 FY2008 Spring / Summer Fashion Preview, 2007 November 28; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - November 29, 2007 FY2008 Perspective Talk: David Peeler, 2007 November 29; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - December 3, 2007 FY2008 Nancy MacDonnell: In The Know, 2007 December 3; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - December 6, 2007 FY2008 Michael Kammen: Visual Shock, 2007 December 6; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - December 10, 2007 FY2008 Annie Leibovitz Documentary, 2007 December 10; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - December 12, 2007 FY2008 Chihuly on Chihuly, 2007 December 12; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - CANCELED December 13, 2007 FY2008 Daniel Schnyder's Travelling East, 2007 Decembber 13; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - December 13, 2007 FY2007 Perspective Talk: Busssard, 2007 December 13; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - December 18, 2007 FY2008 Archduke Von Hasburg, 2007 December 18; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - December 19, 2007 FY2008 New York Fashion Trip, 2007 December 19; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - January 10, 2008 FY2008 Perspective Talk: Hank Stuever, 2008 January 10; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 25)